总统发表国情咨文时  一名内阁成员会被带到一处秘密地点
若政府遭遇灾难性袭击  该内阁成员将会成为新的总统
他们被称为是  指定幸存者
英雄造时势
There are times when we make history,
时势也造就英雄
and there are times when history makes us.
对我们国家来说  这是一个残酷的时刻
This is a crucial moment for our nation,
当我们全力以赴应对挑战
and America's colors burn brightest
美国的光彩会更加夺目
when we meet challenges head on.
长久以来
For far too long,
当全国99%的人处于困苦之中
the wealthiest 1% have seen their fortunes only grow
最富有的百分之一财富却在增长
while the rest of the nation lies in worry.
那个现象需要改变
That needs to change.
问题是  我们会为此付出什么
The question is, how do we pay for it?
但问题是  我们会为此付出什么
But the question is, how do we pay for it?
这不是我们能够同意的
It's not even in the vicinity of what we agreed on.
不  这不是交换条件
No!This is not a quid pro quo.
这是"照我说的去做
This is "You do what I say when I say it
否则你将承担后果"
or you suffer the consequences."
已经超过睡...
Uh, it's beyond bedti--
佩妮  你得立刻去睡觉了
Penny, y-you need to go to sleep right now.
让我跟她说
Let me talk to her.
不行  你不能跟爸爸说话
No, you can't talk to Dad.
让我来跟她说  给我吧
Let me talk to her. Come on.
不仅是在国内
And not just here at home...
喂
Hello?
嗨  爸爸
Hi, Daddy.
你是谁啊
Who is this?
佩妮
It's Penny.
佩妮是谁
Penny who?
佩妮·柯克曼  你女儿啊
Penny Kirkman, your daughter.
不  不可能
No, that's not possible.
我女儿已经睡着了  我知道
My daughter's asleep, and I know that
我差不多两个小时前给了她一个晚安吻
because I kissed her good night almost two hours ago.
你和妈妈什么时候回来
When are you and Mommy coming home?
那不重要  因为到时候你已经睡着了
It doesn't matter. You're gonna be asleep by then, right?
对吗
Right?
她不能一直不肯睡觉
She can't keep pulling this.
我有个主意
I've got an idea.
如果你现在去睡觉
What if you go to bed right now
明晚让你多玩一个小时  如何
and I let you stay up an extra hour tomorrow night
我们出去散散步
so we can hang out?
-成交吗  -成交
- Sound like a deal? -Deal.
真乖
That's my girl.
亲亲我
Give me a kiss.
晚安  爸爸
Good night, Daddy.
晚安  小豌豆
Good night, little pea.
看  完美
See? All good.
并不
Not all good.
"并不"是什么意思
What do you mean, not all good?
汤姆  你不能那么做
Tom, you can't do that.
你不能承诺你做不到的事
You can't make promises that you won't be able to keep.
我们在华盛顿
We're in Washington.
只能做出这种承诺了
They're the only promises we're allowed to make.
你需要学习怎么给她制定规则
You know, you need to learn how to set some limits with her.
如果不这样做  她会得寸进尺的
Because if not,she is gonna walk all over you.
我知道
I know.
你是对的
You're right.
我们所珍视的价值观
...values that we hold dear,
代表了我们是谁
that represent who we are...
最精彩的部分来了
Here come the greatest hits.
我向大家保证  与我们的父亲母亲
...to ensure you that the same American dream
以及他们的上一辈曾经拥有过的
shared by our fathers, our mothers,
同一个美国梦
and their fathers and --
真奇怪
That's weird.
-怎么了  -没能恢复
- What is it? - It won't come back on.
你试试能弄好吗
See if you can get it to work.
好
Okay.
是我
Yeah.
对  我知道  我们这边的信号也没了
No, I know. Ours just went black, too.
汤姆
Tom!
-我的天啊  -我待会回你
- Oh, my God! -I'll get back to you.
部长先生  放下手机
Mr. Secretary, you need to put the phone down.
-麦克  发生什么事了  -我说放下手机
- Mike,what the hell is going on? - I said put the phone down.
-好  好  -女士  还有你的手机
- Okay, okay. - Ma'am, your phone.
我们跟国会大厦失去了联系
We've lost contact with the Capitol.
在知道更多消息前  我们将就地避难
We're sheltering in place until we know more.
我需要政府发给你的黑莓手机
I need your government-issued BlackBerry.
-什么  -你身上还有其他通讯设备吗
- What? - Do you have any other devices on you?
女士  请检查你的包
Please, check your bag, ma'am.
但是我得...
But I -- but I -- I need --
我们收到消息
We are getting reports
在国会大厦里面或者周边发生了爆炸
of some kind of explosion in or around the Capitol building.
我们仍将...
We are still...
部长先生  马上离开窗户
Mr. Secretary, get away from the window, now!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
第一季
第一集
15小时之前
我以为你说你要睡一会
I thought you said you were gonna get some sleep.
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
最新最快海外影视字幕下载
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
我没事
I'm okay.
翻译：   石头   长颈鹿   大王   吸吸粒   Silence
■
美国国家睡眠基金会建议成年人
National Sleep Foundation recommends seven hours
需要七小时的睡眠以维持身体机能运作
to function as a normal human being.
翻译：  持久   桑葚   ruby   Michael   星星与野狗
一个要上班的母亲只需要四小时
A working mother only needs four.
更正一下  是只能睡四小时
Uh, correction, only gets four.
校对：    小早从小爱MQ   追着MQ的栗子
时间轴：   想念浓子的姜姜   想念浓子的浪影
后期： 虫虫不咬人     总监： 小早从小爱MQ
不  不行
No. No.
-我不会干坏事的  -汤姆  我
- I'm not doing anything. - Tom, I have...
快停下  我要工作
No. Stop it. I have work to do.
我也是  这是个两个人的活儿
So do I, and it's a two-person job.
来嘛  你说你会永远支持我的
Come on. You've always said you're always on my side.
这就对了
Yes.
这才是我想要的
That's all I want.
-妈妈  -别  别啊
- Mom! - No, no, no, no.
快走开
Go away!
爸爸  快出来
Dad! Get out here!
好饿呀  我想吃早餐
I'm hungry! I want some breakfast!
不要打扰我们  我们不爱你啦
Leave us alone! You are not loved!
拜托啦
Please!
-别啊  -你在开玩笑嘛
- No. - Are you kidding?
好吧  你会得到你应得的
Okay. You're gonna get what you deserve.
-我要去做早餐  -不  不  别去
- I'm making breakfast. - No. No, no, no.
-我要给每个人都煎个烙饼  -别啊
- Pancakes for everyone! - Please, no!
放开我  老婆
Let me go, woman!
天哪
Oh, God.
小姑娘  你想吃咋样的鸡蛋
Okay, little pea. How do you like your eggs?
炒的呢还是炒的呢
Scrambled or scrambled?
那就炒的吧  谢啦
Um, scrambled, please.
很好  坐在柜台上的小美女点的
Excellent. Scrambled eggs coming up
炒鸡蛋马上要好啦
for the beautiful girl sitting at the counter.
来  给你
And there we go.
-谢谢啦  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
李奥  你来得真是时候  吃点什么
Leo. Perfect timing. What do you want?
他在做早餐吗
He's making breakfast?
很不幸  是的
Unfortunately.
我还在这干活呢
Hey, I'm slaving over here.
我吃点吐司算了
I'll just get some toast.
吐司是面包做的  对吧
Toast, toast. That's made with bread, right?
笑一下  你以前听我的笑话都会笑的
Come on. You used to always laugh at my jokes.
那时候我才九岁
I used to be nine.
真是美好的旧时光啊
Ah, the good ol' days.
今晚我需要你照顾一下妹妹  好吗
Hey, I need you to watch your sister tonight, okay?
不  不要  我很忙的
Uh, no. I can't do it. I'm busy.
忙于照顾你妹妹  我懂的
I know. Watching your sister.
拜托  今晚对我来说很重要
Come on. It's a big night for me.
我要看国情咨文演讲
I've got the State of the Union.
今晚对我来说也很重要
Well, it is for me, too.
我要帮迦勒点忙
I told Caleb I'd help him out with something.
-帮啥忙  -这无关紧要
- With what? - It doesn't matter.
是因为我不会喜欢才无关紧要呢
It doesn't matter because I won't like it
还是因为我听不懂
or doesn't matter 'cause I won't understand?
都有点吧
Both.
好吧  那我现在真的想知道了
Okay, now I really want to know.
他要制作一张回响贝斯的光盘
He's laying down a new dubstep track,
我得帮他写个程序
and I need to write a program for him.
好吧  是个男的
I understood "him."
我让你难堪到哪个程度了  一到十级
On a scale of 1 to 10, how much do I embarrass you?
-十一级  -很好
- 11. - Excellent.
你的英语论文写完了吗
Hey, you finish your English paper yet?
-构思中  -快写完它
- Uh, in theory. - Finish it.
你可以送他们吧  我要在九点前到法院
You can take them, right? I have to be at court by 9:00.
没问题
Yeah, I got them.
再见  小宝贝
Bye, peanut.
再见  妈妈
Bye, Mommy.
好好干
Make us proud.
美国移民改革法案  但事实上不幸的是
...immigration reform, but the sad truth of the matter
今晚里士满可以允诺他想通过的一切政策法案
is that Richmond can promise all he wants tonight.
里士满总统今晚将发表国情咨文演讲
但国会是不会帮他半点忙的
This Congress isn't gonna lift a finger to help him.
如果这事不能等到我回办公室再说的话
Well, this can't be good if it won't even wait
那就铁定不是好事了
till I get to the office.
像世界末日般糟糕的事
How about the end of days?
我刚和内阁事务处的吉林斯谈过
I just spoke to Gillings at Cabinet Affairs.
他向我透露了里士满的演讲稿最终版里
He slipped me a final copy of Richmond's address
一丁点都没有提到我们的观点
and none, not a single one of our talking points are included.
你在逗我吧
You're kidding me.
连住房改革都没提吗
Not even housing reform?
没有  我们几个月以来
All of it, everything you and I
-起早摸黑干的活全白费了  -好吧
- have worked our asses off on for months, gone. - Okay, okay.
尽快给我安排和朗顿的会面
Just get me a meeting with Langdon as soon as possible.
安排好了  我们现在就去
Already done. We're going there now.
是时候去撕逼了
It's time to war up.
冷静点  汉尼拔[著名美剧里的杀人狂]
Easy, Hannibal.
如果会面没有进展的话  我们也该考虑一下
We should also talk about leaking your plan to Politico
-把提案透露给政治报  -这会适得其反的
- if this doesn't work. - No, that'll backfire.
可能吧  但至少被人知晓了啊
Maybe, but it'll be out there.
今晚最重要的是国情咨文里提到的内容
Tonight is about what's in the State of the Union,
没被提到的东西没人会在乎的
not what's not.
我们不能让白宫随便
We can't just let the White House take an eraser
抹去我们整份内政议程
to our entire domestic agenda.
你可是住房与城市发展部的部长啊
You're the Secretary of Housing and Urban Development.
这是总统的内政议程  小艾
It's the President's domestic agenda, Em.
是你的内政议程  部长先生
It's your domestic agenda, Mr. Secretary.
好吧  我尽量争取
Okay, and I'll make my argument for it.
别误会
Look, don't get me wrong.
我也很生气  但话说回来
I'm as mad as hell. But at the end of the day,
我并不是美国总统
I'm not the President of the United States.
别忘了这点
We should remember that.
好吧  那我们去见幕僚长吧
All right. Then let's go see the Chief of Staff.
-非常感谢  -谢谢  长官
- Thank you very much. - Thank you, sir.
我们得告诉美国人民我们的成果
We need to tell the American people how we're doing,
得说的具体一点
and we need to get specific.
谁能给我一个重型武器
Could one of you please find me something heavy
让我揍晕怀特先生  谢谢
to hit Mr. Wright with? Thank you.
相信我  我们得再看看AB-33部分
I'm telling you. We need to take a look at the AB-33 section,
好吗  写得太乱了
okay? The message is muddled.
我自己写的都不知道是在讲什么
I wrote it, and I don't even know what it says.
这就是优秀政治演讲稿的标志
That is the mark of - a successful political speech.
做得好  继续工作吧
Well done. Now, go forth.
-欢迎  部长先生  跟我来  -查理
- Mr. Secretary, welcome. Please. - Charlie.
你还记得亚伦·肖尔吧  我的副幕僚长
I'm sure you remember Aaron Shore, my Deputy Chief of Staff.
-亚伦  很高兴见到你  -部长先生
- Aaron, good to see you. - Mr. Secretary.
我大胆猜一下  你来不是为了
I'm gonna hazard a guess and say you're not here
讨论今晚总统要戴什么颜色的领带吧
to discuss which color tie the President is wearing tonight.
那是他自己的决定
That is his call...
如果他能把部长的住房提按重新提上议程的话
if he'll put back in the Secretary's housing initiatives.
这些项目能帮助上百万低收入家庭
These are programs that can help millions of low-income families.
没人否认它的价值  艾米丽
No one's debating its value here, Emily.
查理  今晚的演讲
Charlie, there's not a single mention
我的项目一点都没有提到吗
of any of my programs in the speech tonight?
-一个都没有吗  -我很抱歉  部长先生
- Not a one? - I know. I'm sorry, Mr. Secretary,
但木已成舟  演讲稿已经写好了
but that's how it's gonna be. The speech is locked.
总统在乎部长的看法吗  查理
Does the President value the Secretary's opinion, Charlie?
因为现在根本看不出来
Because right now, it's hard to tell.
小艾
Em.
让我们单独谈谈
Give us a moment.
在外面等我
I'll meet you outside.
怎么回事  查理
What's going on, Charlie?
汤姆  我们本该等
Well, Tom, we were gonna wait till after
国情咨文时再通知你
the State of the Union to tell you this,
但总统希望能做出改变
but the President's looking to make a change.
他想让你出任
He would like to offer you an ambassadorship
国际民用航空组织大使
to the International Civil Aviation Organization.
你开玩笑吗
Are you serious?
不能让国际煎饼主席
Was the Chairman of the International House
出任这个职位吗
of Pancakes unavailable?
汤姆
Tom...
我真的没想到会是这个情况
This is really not how I saw today going.
民用航空委员会
The Civil Aviation Committee --
-组织  -组织
- Organization. - Organization.
真有这种组织吗  查理
Is that even a real thing, Charlie?
当然有
Of course it's a thing.
在蒙特利尔  受联合国监管
It's in Montreal. It's under the U.N.
听着  这能让你享受到大使的待遇
Look, it affords you the rank of ambassador
还有所有的附加好处
with all the trimmings that go along with it.
得了吧  查理  我们在这做的挺好的
Come on, Charlie. We've done some good work here.
还有很多未竟之事
And we've got lots left to do, I mean --
总统的整个任期
I have supported this president
我都全力支持着他
above and beyond for his entire term.
现在事关下一个任期
Well, now it's about the second term.
我的职责就是让总统满意
And I serve at the pleasure of the President.
你也一样  汤姆
So do you, Tom.
他们不知道你对他们来说多么重要吗
Don't they realize what a huge asset you are for them?
朗顿想把这当作是提拔
Langdon actually tried to pass it off as a promotion.
你不能就这么逆来顺受
Uh, you can't take this lying down.
-那你想让我怎么办  -抗争
- How else do you want me to take it? - Fight.
听着  他能任命你  但他不能解雇你
Look, he appointed you, but he can't fire you.
你要坚持自己的阵地
You need to hold your ground.
你想让我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
跟美国总统闹翻吗
Go to war with the President of the United States?
白宫从来没尊重过你
The White House never respected you.
这才是问题所在
That's the real problem.
不  艾丽克斯  问题在于
No, Alex. The real problem is
我不是一直都听里士满的话
I didn't play Richmond's game all the time.
得了吧  汤姆
Oh, Tom, come on!
政治就是这样
It's called politics.
-就算你听了  -怎么
- And maybe if you did -- - What?
我就不会丢了这份工作吗
I wouldn't be out of a job?
也许吧  但我就会像其他俯首听命的人一样
Maybe, but then I'd be just like one of those guys,
我接受这份工作的时候就谈好了
and when I got into this, we had a deal.
我不会成为那样的人
I wasn't gonna be one of those guys.
-我不想成为  -汤姆  已经三年了
- I don't want to be -- - Tom, it's taken three years.
我们终于在华盛顿安定下来
And we finally settled into Washington.
我爱我的工作
I love my job.
佩妮也很喜欢她的学校
Penny loves her school.
就连李奥也交到了朋友
Even Leo's making friends.
我们不能让这个家庭承受这些
We can't do this to our family.
我知道
I know.
你说得对
You're right.
过来抱抱
Come here. Come here.
我爱你
I love you.
我们可以的
We'll make this work.
我可以两边跑
I'll commute.
什么
What?
你已经决定了是吗
So, you've made up your mind?
就这样离开岗位
You're stepping down?
我跟他们说明天再回复
I told them I'd give them my decision tomorrow.
艾丽克斯
Alex.
这下好了
Great.
指定幸存者是什么
What's a designated survivor?
部长先生  我们得马上离开
Mr. Secretary, we need to leave now.
-汤姆  -你看到了吗
- Tom! - Did you see that?
搜查车辆  排除埋伏可能
...motorcade to smoke out any ambush.
白宫安全  快走
White House is secure. Let's go.
麦克  把你了解的情况都告诉我们吧
Mike, please, just tell us what you know.
国会大厦受到袭击
Capitol's been attacked.
总统和他的保镖还没有音讯
There's still no word on the President or his detail.
我是里特
This is Ritter.
天  不会吧
Oh, God. Don't tell me that.
什么情况
What is it?
消息已证实
It's confirmed.
总统死了
Eagle is gone.
-整个国会  内阁  -天啊
- Congress, the Cabinet. - Oh, oh, my God.
无人幸免
None of them made it.
遵命
Yes, sir.
我会告知他
I'll let him know.
部长先生  我们将遵循政府的连续性原则
Mr. Secretary, we're enacting continuity of government.
特区上诉法院会派一名法官到白宫跟我们见面
A D.C. Appellate judge will meet us at the White House.
先生  你现在是美国总统了
Sir, you are now the President of the United States.
国会大厦发生大规模爆炸  新闻大事件
美国国会大厦一片火海
The United States Capitol Building in flames.
就在刚才
An explosion -- should I say an unconfirmed explosion --
总统里士满发表国情咨文演说时
going off just moments ago
发生了一起爆炸  爆炸还未得到官方证实
during President Richmond's State of the Union address.
毫无疑问我们将
Of course, we're reaching out
动用全部资源...
to all of our sources...
接电话  快
Pick up. Come on.
你好  我是斯科特  有事无法接电话
Hi. This is Scott. I'm not available right now.
请在滴声后留言
Please leave me a message after the beep.
是我
Hey, it's me.
听到后打给我
Call me when you get this.
让我知道你没事
I need to know you're okay.
斯科特
Hey, Scott?
不  我是道格  我需要你马上过来
No, it's Doug. I need you here right away.
好的  我马上过来
Yes, sir. I'm on my way.
-夫人  -得把我的孩子接过来
- Ma'am... - We got to get our kids here.
已经派人去接了
We've already sent agents to bring them here.
我们还在努力获取信息
We are still working to get all the information
弄清事情真相...
of exactly what happened...
这边请
Sir, please.
夫人  请拿好圣经
Ma'am, please hold the Bible.
拿好圣经  谢谢
Just hold the Bible. Thank you.
先生  将你左手放在圣经上  跟我宣誓
Sir, place your left hand on the Bible and repeat after me.
我  托马斯·亚当·柯克曼  庄严宣誓
"I, Thomas Adam Kirkman, do solemnly swear..."
I, Thomas Adam Kirkman, do solemnly swear...
我必忠实执行
"...that I will faithfully execute the office
美利坚合众国总统职务
of President of the United States..."
我必忠实执行
...that I will faithfully execute the office
美利坚合众国总统职务
of President of the United States...
竭尽全力
"...and will, to the best of my ability..."
...and will, to the best of my ability...
恪守  维护和捍卫
"...preserve, protect, and defend
美利坚合众国宪法
the Constitution of the United States."
恪守  维护和捍卫
...preserve, protect, and defend
美利坚合众国宪法
the Constitution of the United States,
上帝保佑
so help me God.
总统先生  夫人
Mr. President. Ma'am.
总统先生  跟我走
Mr. President, you're gonna have to come with me now.
柯克曼夫人
Mrs. Kirkman, the Secret Service
特勤局会送你到住所
will take you up to the residence now.
-夫人  请跟我走  -总统先生
- Ma'am, please come with me. - Mr. President.
-快  -请
- Right now. - Please.
亚伦  我们这是去哪
Aaron, where are we going?
总统紧急行动中心
The Presidential Emergency Operations Center.
世界范围内的所有队伍
...every team we have worldwide.
我要所有人时刻准备
I want every drone waiting on full staff
-接到命令立即执行  -打扰一下
- and deployable as soon as they get the order. - Excuse me.
能做到吗
Can you do that?
分配下去
Well, get it done.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
全都安静一下
I need you all to be quiet right now.
麻烦了
Please.
请大家花一点时间悼念我们逝去的
Let's take a moment for our fallen friends,
每一位朋友  英雄
heroes one and all.
谢谢
Thank you.
也许我们应该四处慰问一下
Maybe we should go around the table.
中情局主管呢
Where's the CIA director?
我们还在建立安全通讯
We're still working to set up a secure comm.
别管安全通讯了
The hell with secure comms.
我们眼下必须帮他转接进来
We have to get him patched in now --
手机  座机  网络电话  随便一种
cellphone, landline, Skype -- whatever we got.
谁有网络可用
Who's got the networks?
好吧  告诉他们接下来的六十分钟
Okay, you tell them we'll be live in 60 minutes
我们会待在白宫东屋
from the East Room, okay?
不准向任何机构媒体或部门透露任何消息
Nobody talks to any press of any office or agency
否则我把你们生吞活剥了
under threat of me ripping your insides out.
知不知道始作俑者是谁
Do we know - who's responsible for this?
现在下定论还为之尚早
Still too early to determine.
我们得给大家一个交代  凯伦
We got to give them something, Karen.
现在全世界都在关注我们
The whole world is watching us right now.
没错  每个小时都要向大使馆发出警报
Exactly. We need to alert every one of our embassies
让每个东道国知道
to convey to each host nation
美国即将宣告战争开始
that the U.S. is on a war footing
现在不要考验我们的底线
and now is not the time to test us.
帮我转接五角大楼全天候监视处
Patch me into 24-hour watch at the Pentagon.
通知幸存的联席国家元首
Inform the surviving joint chiefs
我们即将进入二级戒备状态
we are going to DEFCON 2.
你不能做这个决定
You can't make that call.
联席会议主席已经不在了
The Chairman of the Joint Chiefs is gone.
这不是代表你有这个职权  哈里斯
That doesn't give you any authority, Harris.
我们正遭受袭击  还需要什么职权
We're under attack. What more authority do you want?
你以为你是谁
Who do you think you are?
我要美国空军十五分钟后起飞
I want the Air Force flying in 15 minutes.
你有什么权利给我下命令
Who are you to give me orders?
你凭什么质疑他们  彼得
Who are you to question them, Peter?
我不会干坐着  期待事情好转
I'm not gonna sit on my ass and hope for the best here.
全吐出来吧
Let it all out, man.
今晚我们的感受都一样
We're all feeling the same way tonight.
抱歉  我以为这里只有我一个人
Sorry. I thought I was alone.
事情已非表面的那样了
Yeah, well, nothing is what it seems anymore.
一小时前  我在狂吐龙舌兰酒
You know, an hour ago, I was throwing back tequila,
庆祝一万字的演讲稿里有我写的三行稿子
celebrating the three lines I got into a 10,000-word speech.
我向天发誓  我不知道
Swear to God, I don't know how the hell
我们到底要如何度过这个艰难时刻
we're gonna get through this.
和以往一样
Same way we always do.
没错
Yeah, right.
我们是否知道  现在由谁来主持大局
Do you even know - who's in charge right now?
我这么问  是因为我根本不记得他的名字
I'm asking, because - I can't even remember his name.
柯克曼  汤姆·柯克曼
Kirkman. Tom Kirkman.
对  柯克兰  没错
Oh, yeah, yeah. Kirkland. That's right.
权限最低的职员
The lowest rung on the ladder.
你知道今早里士满总统把他革职了吗
Did you know President Richmond fired him this morning?
而他现在却成了总统
Now he's the President.
在这个国家最黑暗的时期
He's the one the country's gonna be turning to
他是我们唯一的选择
in our darkest hour.
也许他会出人意料
Well, maybe he'll surprise you.
你是说也许他会意识到
Yeah, you mean maybe he'll realize
他没资格治理这个国家吗
he has no business running the country?
那他应该退位让贤
That he should just step aside,
找个将军或中情局主管来接手
maybe let one of the generals take over or the CIA director,
至少他们知道自己在做什么
somebody who actually knows what the hell they're doing?
这个可能性非常小
Fat chance of that happening.
这里没人会放弃权力
Nobody around here ever gives up power.
柯克兰只是个跟班
Kirkland's a follower.
我们需要的是带头人
We need a leader.
我告诉你  我有点想跑去加拿大
I'm telling you, man, I got half a mind to make a run to Canada.
明白我的意思吗
You know what I'm saying?
加拿大
Canada.
总统先生
Uh, Mr. President.
你刚刚说的话真的是你所想吗
Do you really believe everything you just said?
总统先生  请听我解释
Uh, Mr. President, let me explain.
你叫什么
What's your name?
赛斯·怀特
Seth Wright.
赛斯·怀特  你是演讲稿撰写人
Seth Wright. You're a speechwriter.
我看到你今早从查理的办公室出来
I saw you coming out of Charlie's office earlier this morning.
你们在讨论总统演讲稿
You were arguing about the President's address.
AB33节
Uh, the AB-33 section.
住房改革
Housing reform.
你真的认为我应该让位吗
You really think I should step down?
是的
I do.
也许你是对的
You may be right.
但目前而言  我是你们唯一的选择
But for now, I'm all you got,
你有整整五十二分钟
and you have...
可以写演讲稿
exactly 52 minutes to write a speech
来说服美国民众这是明智之举
convincing the American people that that's a good thing.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
佩妮
Penny!
妈妈
Mommy!
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
大家都听好了
All right, listen up.
没有警徽  谁也不允许进出
No one comes in or out without tin.
在至少五个街口以外设置警戒线
I want a secure perimeter, at least five blocks out.
并部署安检装置
I want TSA screening equipment installed now.
-明白了吗  -是
- Got it? -Yes, sir.
好了  大家继续工作
All right, back to work.
还要发射热成像无人机和空中嗅探器
You'll also want to send up thermo UAVs and air sniffers
检查此区域内所有生物及放射物
to look for anything biological or radiological in the area.
汉娜  你怎么没向总部汇报
Hannah, you were supposed to report to HQ.
我当时隔了十个街区
I was 10 blocks away.
有幸存者吗
Any survivors?
暂时没有
No, not yet.
急救小队正在废墟里挖
EMS is digging through the rubble.
让危险品处理组...
Make sure that Haz-Mat knows --
威尔士探员  你是科技情报行动中心的人
Agent Wells, you're SIOC, okay,
不是外勤探员
you're not a field agent.
你去指挥中心领导一支应急小组
I need you heading up a crisis team at the operations center.
在电脑后面待着没用  这里更需要我
Don't need me behind a computer. You need me here.
-我现场处理过... -汉娜
- I worked both bomb sites... - Hannah --
布鲁塞尔和巴黎爆炸案
...on the ground in Brussels and Paris.
我知道应该怎么做
I know what to look for.
杰森
Jason...
拜托  我得留在这
please, I need to be here.
诺兰  劳伦斯
Nolan. Lawrence.
是  副局长
Yes, Deputy Director?
你们听威尔士指挥
You're with Wells.
有人宣称负责吗
Anyone claiming responsibility?
目前没有
No, not yet.
埃里克  我需要这周边三个街区内
All right, Eric, I want the license plates
所有汽车的车牌号
of every car parked in the next three blocks scanned.
如果有失窃车辆或者车主属于监视对象的
If any of them are stolen or owned by anyone on a watch list,
把它大卸八块
you tear that car apart.
马克  联系排爆工程师  现场调查组
Mark, bomb disposal techs, CSI,
把发现的东西分类  标记好发现地点
we catalog what we find and where we found it.
开工吧
Let's move.
托马斯·亚当·柯克曼
Thomas Adam Kirkman was born
生于1967年12月29日
December 29th, 1967,
汤姆·柯克曼是谁
出生于纽约华盛顿港
in Port Washington, New York.
在被任命为住房和城市发展部
Before being appointed secretary of Housing
部长之前
and Urban Development,
柯克曼曾在学术界从事教育工作
Kirkman worked in academia as an educator.
简直疯了
This is insane.
他这职位算什么
Guy's never been elected to anything.
住房和城市发展部
He ran HUD.
给人们提供住得起的房子
They find affordable homes for people,
柯克曼不过是个说得好听的地产中介
which makes Kirkman a glorified real-estate agent.
他是现在第一顺位继承人
He was next in the line of succession.
不好意思  这事谁也预料不到
I'm sorry, but no one could have foreseen this.
为什么你会觉得
Why the hell do you think
有一个指定幸存者呢  尼基
there's a designated survivor, Nikki?
因为这是可以预见的
Because this was foreseen.
闭嘴别打扰我干活
Now shut up and let me work.
你在外面干什么
What are you doing out here?
我想静一静
I just needed a minute.
佩妮还好吗
How's Penny?
天哪
Ah, God.
害怕  迷惑
Scared. Confused.
我想跟所有人一样吧
You know, I mean, just like everyone, I guess.
这是真的吗
Is this even happening?
我在这干什么  艾丽克斯
What the hell am I doing here, Alex?
我干不了这个
I'm not the guy for this.
你想放弃吗
You want to quit?
我知道这么说不对
I know it's not the right thing to say,
但我禁不住觉得...
but I can't help but feel --
就像为了逃命一样
Like running for our lives.
是啊
Yeah.
汤姆  也许我们真该放弃
Tom, maybe we should.
看看今晚发生的一切
Look what happened tonight.
多少人...  我们都没来得及消化
How many people -- we haven't even processed.
还有我们的孩子
And our kids?
我们要让他们置身危险之中吗
Are we putting them in danger?
我是说...
I mean...
我们现在成了目标
We're a target now.
他们呢
Are they?
我不知道
I-I-I don't know --
-总统先生  -怎么了
- Mr. President. - Yeah?
你说李奥今晚在朋友家
You said Leo was at a friend's house tonight.
在迦勒·韦斯特那里
Yeah, Caleb West.
我刚跟去他家的特工通过电话
I just spoke to our agents at his residence
李奥不在那儿
and Leo wasn't there.
他根本没去他家
He never was.
什么
What?
那他在哪里
Where is he?
我们也不知道
We don't know.
他们会找到李奥的
They're gonna find Leo.
迈克了解他
Mike knows him.
特勤局  这方面他们是全世界最厉害的
Secret Service -- they're the best in the world at this.
我知道
I know.
总统先生  这边请
Mr. President. This way, please.
稍等一下
Please give me a sec.
我能挺住
I got this.
您请
After you.
这位是卡梅伦少校
This is Major Cameron.
总统先生  这是核钥匙
Mr. President, this is the nuclear football.
您每次离开白宫都需随身携带
It'll be with you whenever you leave the White House.
这些是发射密码  验证密码
These are the launch codes, verification codes,
能够发射核武器的
a listing of every classified location
发射井位置列表...
capable of launching nuclear weapons.
一旦发生袭击
In the event of an imminent strike,
你可以使用这个电话来下达指令
you can green-light it using this phone.
在地球的任何地方甚至地下它都能工作
It works anywhere on Earth as well as beneath it.
需要我的指纹或眼球扫描或其他什么吗
Do you need my fingerprints or an eye scan or something?
不  先生  这和电影里不一样
No, sir. It's not like the movies.
不是那样操作的
It doesn't work that way.
当然
Of course.
总统先生  联合国正在召开紧急会议
Mr. President, the UN is in emergency session.
我这里有三页长的电话清单
I have a three-page phone list
我们每一个敌对国都打电话来
with every one of our enemies calling
声称与这次袭击无关
to deny responsibility for the attack.
所有美国军事基地已进入最高警戒状态
All US military bases are on full alert,
艾森豪威尔舰正火速前往
and the USS Eisenhower is currently hard charging
驻扎在波斯湾的美国第五舰队基地
towards the Fifth Fleet stationed in the Persian Gulf.
军事基地进入警戒状态我可以理解
I understand alerting our bases,
可是我们为什么要派航母火速前往某处
but why are we "Hard charging" a US aircraft carrier anywhere?
总统先生  如果发生袭击--
Mr. President, in the event of an attack --
被谁袭击
An attack from who?
你刚才说了  所有敌对国都声称与此事无关
Y-You just said all our enemies are denying responsibility.
因为所有战争都是尔虞我诈的
Because all warfare is based on deception
还有很多信息我们没有得到
and there are still plenty we haven't heard from.
我只是觉得还没到要动用如此武力的地步
I just don't feel comfortable showing that kind of force yet.
恕我直言  先生
With all due respect, sir,
你是否可以告诉我们
would you mind telling us
你认为什么时候才合适
when you do plan on being comfortable?
我会在第一时间告诉你  将军
You'll be the first to know, General.
失陪
Excuse me.
很高兴和你做生意
Pleasure doing business with you.
♪Freedom take me tonight♪
♪Staring up at the sky♪
♪I’m heaven bound♪
你还有几包
So, how many more bags you got?
我刚把最后两包卖掉
I just sold my last two.
还剩三包
Still got three left.
留着吧  我们得去蹦迪了
Save 'em. We got to bounce anyway.
糟了
Screw that.
♪I’m up in the air♪
我是过来挣钱和寻开心的
I came here to make money and have some fun.
♪Nothing's ever been so clear♪
-李奥  -放开我
- Leo! - Get off me, man!
♪Nothing's ever been so clear♪
麦克
Mike?
♪I’m up in the air♪
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here?
你怎么找到我的
How'd you find me?
费了点功夫
It wasn't easy.
我们不得不开放国安局的一个数据中心
We had to open up an ops center at NSA,
通过"棱镜"来搜索你的朋友同学
run the phone records of all your friends and classmates
和同学的电话记录
through PRISM
最后把足够的聊天关键词拼凑起来
till we could piece together enough chatter keywords
才分析出你的踪迹  找到夜总会来
to trace your digital footprint to the club.
真的吗
Really?
假的  李奥
No, Leo.
我们定位了你的手机
We pinged your phone.
你可不是个当罪犯的料
You're not exactly a criminal mastermind.
我还以为你要带我回家
I thought you were taking me home.
没错
I am.
所有人都惊讶得说不出话
Everyone is at a complete loss for words.
这是自911事件以来最具毁灭性的袭击事件
This is the most devastating attack on our country since 9/11.
白宫里的职员们
And staffers at the White House
也和国民一样  问着同样的问题
are asking the same question as the rest of the country.
究竟是谁幕后操纵了这场可怕的恐怖行动
Who's behind - this horrific act of terror?
你能再检查一下吗
Look, can you please just check again?
我叫艾米丽·罗迪斯
My name is Emily Rhodes.
我是柯克曼秘书的办公室主任
I am Secretary Kirkman's Chief of Staff.
他是今晚的指定幸存者
He was the designated survivor tonight.
我已经说过你不在安全名单上
Look, I already told you you're not on the cleared list.
我今天早上还在里面
I was just in there this morning.
那之后发生了很多事
Well, a lot's happened since then,
可能你还没有注意到
in case you haven't noticed.
退回到大门那边
Step back from the gate.
情报处对于今天在国会大厦
Intelligence sources are being tight-lipped
发生的事情守口如瓶
about what has happened at the Capitol today,
目前为止  没有人声称负责
but as of yet, no one has claimed responsibility
我们国家保持高度警戒状态
and our nation remains on high alert.
感谢你的祈祷  首相夫人
Thank you for your prayers, Madam Prime Minister.
你也一样
You, too.
再见
Goodbye.
好  刚才说到哪儿了
Right, where were we?
有总统威严的声音
the presidential voice.
显然我没有
Which, apparently, I don't have.
你可以随时帮我说两句
You can defend my honor at any time.
我会的...如果我不同意他说的话
I will...when he says something I disagree with.
好吧  你认为有总统威严的声音是怎样的
Okay, so, what do you think the presidential voice is?
"我们所有人都清楚我们有义务要履行
"All of us here know there is work to be done.
我们有责任保护所有美国公民
We have a responsibility to light the way for every American."
我觉得不错
Sounds good to me.
当然了  这是你两年前说过的
I imagine it would. You said it two years ago
两年前  在亚特兰大一个新城市主义的会上
two years ago, in Atlanta at the Conference for the New Urbanism.
总统先生  今晚
Sir, tonight,
你要面对全世界发表讲话
you're speaking to the world.
美国现在不需要其他朋友
America doesn't need another friend right now.
你不能表现得放松或友善
You can't be relaxed or disarming.
这一套已经没用了
That's not gonna work anymore.
总统先生  你必须展现出
Mr. President, you need to be stronger
前所未有的坚强
than you've ever been before.
现在我们都要更加坚强
We all need that right now.
发生什么了  汤姆
What is it, Tom?
我要走了
I've got to go.
坐下吧
Just sit down.
没事的  我们都有这种感觉
It's okay. We're all feeling it.
谢谢  夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
艾力克斯  别这样
Alex, please.
不  夫人
no, ma'am.
你现在是第一夫人
You're the First Lady.
不  不用站起来  坐吧
No, no. Please, sit down.
卫星图像显示  10艘伊朗海军驱逐舰
Sat imagery shows - 10 Iranian Navy destroyers
正要驶离阿巴斯港
leaving Bandar Abbas port
并沿霍尔木兹海峡就位
and taking up positions along the Strait of Hormuz.
霍尔木兹海峡
The Strait of Hormuz
全世界百分之三十的石油运输时要经过这里
is where 30% of the world's oil passes through.
这我知道  亚伦
I know what it is, Aaron.
总统先生
Mr. President,
这是伊朗的一场有预谋的挑衅
this is a purposeful provocation by the Iranians
准备利用今晚的事件
to take advantage of the night's events
切断西方世界的石油主要供给
and choke off the Western world's main supply of oil.
在我们焦头烂额的时候
Just as we're on our knees,
他们要致我们于死地
they're gonna step on our throat.
亚伦
Aaron.
我总算进来了
I finally got past the gate.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
我现在不方便说话  艾米丽
I can't talk right now, Emily.
我要回到总统紧急行动中心
I need to get back to the PEOC.
汤姆会去开会吗
Is Tom gonna be in there?
当然  这是他的会议
Well, it is his meeting.
那我跟你一起去
Well, then I'm coming with you.
对不起  艾米丽
Sorry, Emily,
但那里必须说暗号才能通过
but in there, it's code-word clearance only.
我跟国务卿柯克曼的手下一起工作三年了
I've been with Secretary Kirkman's staff for three years.
现在是柯克曼总统了
It's President Kirkman now,
而且你并没得到授权
and you're not authorized.
如果你想现在搞这种无聊的竞争  亚伦
If you are choosing this moment for a pissing contest, Aaron --
这就是我的意思  艾米丽
That's my point, Emily.
这不是什么竞争
This is no contest.
不好意思  我现在要走了
Now, if you'll excuse me --
柯克曼总统需要他熟悉的人在身边
President Kirkman needs people he knows by his side.
我们之间有点分歧
You and I have our differences.
我明白  你不想我进去那里
I know. And you don't want me in there.
但你比其他人更清楚
But you also know better than anyone else
此刻有我在那里支持他很重要
why it is important that I am there for him right now.
我要怎么说你才能明白
How many more ways can I say this?
明天早上  我们的经济就会急剧下滑
In the morning, our economy is going to go over a cliff,
而伊朗人正想抓住这个机会
and the Iranians are just seizing the moment.
你想让我怎么做  将军
What do you want me to do, General?
发动战争
Declare war?
干嘛不呢
Why not?
四十分钟前  他们给我看了核提箱
40 minutes ago, they showed me the nuclear football.
是时候来试试威力了
I guess I've had it long enough to try it out.
我们被袭击了
We've just been attacked.
全世界都把这看作是对我们的试探
The world thinks it can test us right now,
全力快速的武力展示
and a full, swift show of force
是唯一可以提醒他们
is the only way to remind them
美国仍然屹立不倒的方式
that our flag is still flying strong tonight.
我的意思是我觉得
And all I'm saying is that I think
展示武力有很多不同方式
there are different ways to show force.
你要知道
What you need to understand
伊朗人只会在乎一种行动
is the Iranians respect only one course of action,
那就是采取武力
and that is action.
这可不是什么消费者组织
This is not some consumer group
等着跟名誉领袖合影的小打小闹
waiting for a photo op with a figurehead.
名誉领袖
Figurehead.
好吧  将军
Well, General,
这个名誉领袖在内阁会议期间
this figurehead paid attention during the Cabinet meetings,
专门关注过这个问题
where we dealt with this very issue.
伊朗人在过去35年中一直在尝试
And the Iranians have tried to close off the Strait of Hormuz
封锁霍尔木兹海峡
for the last 35 years,
所以我很难相信
so I am having a difficult time believing
他们突然决定今晚就封
that they just up and decided to do that tonight.
你怎么确定他们不会
And how can you be so certain of that?
伊朗大使预计什么时候到
When is the Iranian ambassador due to arrive?
15分钟后
15 minutes.
好的  将军
Okay, General.
你可以下令让你的轰炸机起飞
You can scramble your bombers,
但并不是开战
but they are not to engage.
我们要按照我说的来做
We are going to do this my way.
如果行不通  就按照你的来
If it doesn't work, we'll try yours.
我知道你吓坏了  亲爱的
I know you're scared, peanut,
一切都会好起来的
but everything's gonna be okay.
但为什么我们在这里
But why are we here?
因为这里  这里会是我们的新家
'Cause this, uh -- - this is gonna be our new home.
为什么
But why?
因为今晚有些坏人做了一些坏事
Because some bad people did something bad tonight,
老爸的职责就是确保我们都安全
and it's Dad's job to make sure we're all safe.
你害怕吗
Are you scared?
害怕
Yeah.
爸爸呢
Is Daddy?
开什么玩笑
Are you kidding?
爸爸什么都不怕
Dad's not scared of anything.
我是斯科特
This is Scott.
现在没空
I'm not available right now.
请在哔声后留言
Please leave me a message after the beep.
还是我
It's me again.
你在哪
Where are you?
给我回电话  让我知道你没事
Please call me back and -- and tell me you're okay.
我爱你
I love you.
威尔士探员  我一直在找你
Agent Wells. I was looking for you.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
你有朋友遇难了吗
Did you lose someone?
我想大家都可能失去亲人
I think we all lost someone.
你有什么发现
What do you got?
我查了这片区域里所有车的车牌
I-I checked all the license plates in the area
跟各种监视名单都对比了
against every watch list.
目前没有什么发现
Nothing so far.
好的  跟国安局联系
All right, get in touch with the NSA.
确认他们知道...
Make sure that they know --
我们这里有发现
We got something over here!
-什么情况  -这里有未引爆的爆炸物
- What do we got? - UXO! We got a UXO!
所有人离开那块区域
Clear the perimeter!
好的  离开那块区域
All right. Clear the area!
我们发现了一颗炸弹
We've got a bomb!
往后退
Back up now!
离开那块区域
Clear the area now!
这里已经安全了
Perimeter is secure.
你们可以开始了
You may proceed.
收到
Copy that.
一切就绪  打开吧
All clear. Open it up.
好的  正在拆除外壳
Okay. Removing the outer case.
钳子
Hemostat.
能看到什么
What do you see?
导线连着引信舱
Wires to the fuze compartment,
连着保险弹簧
to the creep spring,
连着炸药
to the detonator.
不过没有压板
But no pressure plate.
慢点
Easy.
没事了
It's clear.
是颗哑弹
Bomb's a dud.
他来了吗
Is he here?
是的  他就在外面等着
Yes, he's -- he's waiting just outside.
让他进来
Send him in.
大使先生
Mr. Ambassador.
总统先生
Mr. President.
请坐
Please.
谢谢
Thank you.
首先请允许我
Please, allow me to begin
向您以及全体美国人民
by extending to you and the American people
对这起不幸的事件
my country's most sincere sympathies
表达我国最真挚的慰问
on this horrific tragedy.
如果有什么需要我们
If there is anything our people can do
对这种极端的懦夫行为给予回应
in response to this tremendous act of cowardice,
请放心  我们一定做到
rest assured, we will do it.
非常感谢
I appreciate that.
你们可以先把在霍尔木兹海峡的
You can begin by removing your destroyers
驱逐舰撤离出去
from the Strait of Hormuz.
总统先生  不好意思
Mr. President, excuse me,
我相信你的信息有误
but I believe you have been misinformed.
是吗
Is that a fact?
是的  我们  我们
Yes. We -- we have moved
从没有往霍尔木兹海峡派任何驱逐舰
no such destroyers into the Strait of Hormuz.
我们国防部的人已经进行过这种演习了
My defense department has war-gamed this out.
他们正等着我的批准
They're waiting for me to give them the green light,
如果在三小时内
which, I assure you, I will do
你们的驱逐舰没有回到阿巴斯港
unless you pull your destroyers back to Bandar Abbas
那么我就会批准这个方案
within the next three hours.
总统先生  我
Mr. President, I would --
大使先生  你可能不是很了解我
Mr. Ambassador, you may not know much about me,
但你应该知道
but what you should know
我是华盛顿
is that I'm about as straight a shooter
最正直坦白的人了
as you're gonna find in Washington.
所以你应该相信我  作为美国的三军统帅
So you should believe me when I tell you that I do not want,
我不想自己下的第一条命令就是攻击伊朗
as my first act as Commander in Chief, to attack Iran.
但是咱俩都清楚
But as both of us know,
有时历史不是由我们决定的
it's not always up to us how history plays itself out.
此时此刻  我相信
Now, I have chosen to believe
伊朗今晚不会有意利用我们的悲伤和恐惧
that your country is not playing on our emotions tonight,
如果不按我的要求去做  你们一定会感受到
but nevertheless, you will feel the full impact of them
这股力量有多么强大
if you do not comply with my demands.
大使先生  让你们的驱逐舰回港
Mr. Ambassador, dock your destroyers
否则明天早晨的头条消息
or the lead story on the morning news
不会是关于美国的国会被袭事件
will not be about the attack on our capital
而是伊朗遭受美国的致命打击
but the devastating attack on yours.
拜托了  大使先生
Please, Mr. Ambassador,
不要让两国关系从一开始就走上歧途
let's not get off on the wrong foot here tonight.
总统先生  我会和我国政府协商的
Mr. President, I will speak with my government.
谢谢你  大使先生
Thank you, Mr. Ambassador.
大使先生  这边请
Mr. Ambassador, this way.
大使先生
Mr. Ambassador.
只有三个小时
Three hours.
进入  安全了
Go in. We're clear.
从来没见过这样的
Haven't seen one of those before.
这是苏联时期的反坦克地雷
It's a Soviet-era anti-tank mine.
在阿富汗还有上千个
There are still thousands of them in Afghanistan.
圣战恐怖组织多年来使用这种地雷作为主要的
Jihadist terror groups have been using them for years
简易爆炸装置
as their primary IEDs.
汉娜  你听到了吗
Hannah, you hearing this?
威尔士探员  炸弹...
Agent Wells, the bomb is --
在你看来  是一颗中东恐怖组织所用的
Is an unexploded munition you think was used
没爆炸的哑弹
by a Mideast terror group --
ISIS  基地组织  或者塔利班
either ISIS, Al-Qaeda, or the Taliban --
来炸毁国会大厦
to blow up our Capitol.
没错  我听到了
Yes, I heard you.
这只是一种可能
And that's one theory.
你还有别的想法吗
You got another one?
这么说吧
All right.
在大袭击事件的前几周
In the weeks leading up to the big ones --
比如9·11  巴黎  比利时
9/11, Paris, Belgium --
我们会接收到异常多的电子通讯情报
the chatter we were getting was off the charts.
一定有大事会发生
Something was coming, you know?
我们只是不知道是什么
We just didn't know what it was.
你知道我现在听到了什么吗
Do you know what I'm hearing now?
什么都没有
Nothing.
我们潜入的清真寺和基地
No breaks in any of the routines
没有任何异常
of the mosques or camps we're inside,
没有人转移自己的妻儿
no one is relocating their wives or children
以防我们反击
in anticipation of our counterattacks.
一切照常
It's business as usual.
这说不通
That makes no sense.
你是说炸弹不是他们的
So, you're saying the bomb isn't one of theirs.
我是说如果是他们所为
I'm saying that if they did this,
他们现在会在庆功
they'd be crowing right now.
罪犯三缄其口
There is a reason the people who did this
是有原因的
are keeping silent about it.
原因是
And that is?
没完事之前你不会居功吧
You don't take credit for something until you're done, right?
如果他们才刚刚开始呢
So, what if - they're just getting started?
我不记得有这件西装
I don't remember this suit.
我借来的
I had to borrow it.
你看起来很像样
You look the part.
我知道这改变了我们的一切
I know this is gonna change everything for us,
但我不得不做
but I have to do it.
如果我不...
If I don't...
我必须要
I just have to.
你还站在我这边吗
You still on my side?
我一直都会站在你那边
I'm always on your side...
总统先生
Mr. President.
得有所行动  亚伦
Something needs to be done, Aaron.
我们已经在尽本分了  哈里斯
I think we're doing everything that's expected of us, Harris.
我不是在说这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
那你到底要说什么
What exactly are you talking about here?
因为如果跟我想的一样
Because if it's what I think it is,
这段对话会和密谋叛国
this conversation's going to be treading dangerously close
有很大关系
to conspiracy to commit treason.
我们现在让住房和城市发展部长
We have a Housing and Urban Development Secretary
掌管着美国
running the free world.
你管它叫叛国
You call it treason.
我管它叫  公民义务
I call it - my civic responsibility.
你说的可是除掉在位总统
You're talking about removing a sitting president.
一个未经选举的总统  没错
An unelected president, yes.
听我说
Listen to me.
如果这个国家要存活
If the country's gonna survive,
我们必须快速果决地行动
we need to act swiftly and definitively.
汤姆·柯克曼是不会带领我们度过危机的
Tom Kirkman will not get us through this.
让我猜猜  你能吗
And let me guess -- You can?
我们在战争状态了
We're in a state of war.
你愿意让谁来领导我们
Who would you rather have leading us?
总统先生
Mr. President.
您的眼镜
Your glasses.
不是很有总统威严  先生
They're not very presidential, sir.
对
Right.
谢谢
Thank you.
总统先生  直播倒数五  四  三...
Mr. President, you're live in five, four, three...
■
人人影视字幕组
官方APP
更新下载手机搞定
讨论交流登陆升级
到各大市场搜索
"人人影视字幕组"
下载网址：app.zimuzu.tv
■
美国民众们
My fellow Americans...